{
   "title": "World Wars",
   "category": "History and Politics",
   "level0": [ {
         "prompt": "Which event triggered the start of World War I?",
         "options": ["Assassination of Archduke Franz Ferdinand", "Invasion of Poland", "Bombing of Pearl Harbor", "Signing of the Treaty of Versailles"],
         "correctAnswer": 0,
         "level": 0
      },
       {
         "prompt": "In which year did World War I end?",
         "options": ["1914", "1917", "1918", "1919"],
         "correctAnswer": 2,
         "level": 0
      },
       {
         "prompt": "Which country was the first to use chemical weapons during World War I?",
         "options": ["Germany", "France", "United States", "Russia"],
         "correctAnswer": 0,
         "level": 0
      },
       {
         "prompt": "Which battle is considered one of the bloodiest of World War I?",
         "options": ["Battle of the Somme", "Battle of Stalingrad", "Battle of Dunkirk", "Battle of Midway"],
         "correctAnswer": 0,
         "level": 0
      },
       {
         "prompt": "Which World War I treaty imposed heavy reparations on Germany and led to economic hardships in the country?",
         "options": ["Treaty of Versailles", "Treaty of Brest-Litovsk", "Treaty of Trianon", "Treaty of Saint-Germain"],
         "correctAnswer": 0,
         "level": 0
      },
       {
         "prompt": "Which country remained neutral during most of World War II?",
         "options": ["United States", "France", "Switzerland", "Italy"],
         "correctAnswer": 2,
         "level": 0
      },
       {
         "prompt": "What was the code name for the Allied invasion of Normandy during World War II?",
         "options": ["Operation Barbarossa", "Operation Market Garden", "Operation Desert Storm", "Operation Overlord"],
         "correctAnswer": 3,
         "level": 0
      },
       {
         "prompt": "Which city was the first target of an atomic bomb during World War II?",
         "options": ["Hiroshima", "Berlin", "Nagasaki", "Tokyo"],
         "correctAnswer": 0,
         "level": 0
      },
       {
         "prompt": "What event triggered the United States' entry into World War II?",
         "options": ["Bombing of London", "Attack on Pearl Harbor", "Invasion of Poland", "Sinking of the Lusitania"],
         "correctAnswer": 1,
         "level": 0
      },
       {
         "prompt": "Which two countries were the primary Axis Powers during World War II?",
         "options": ["Germany and Italy", "Germany and France", "Italy and Japan", "Germany and Japan"],
         "correctAnswer": 3,
         "level": 0
      },
   ],
   "level1": [],
   "level2": [],
   "level3": [],
   "level4": []
}
